the council for national policy is the scariest christian nationalist group you've never heard of
buckle the fuck up for over a year now i've been investigating who is behind all of the anti-trans
anti-lgbtq plus anti-women anti-bipoc bills and laws are being passed in this country and i've
told you about the alliance defending freedom the adf who is behind a lot of the bills but if they
are a henchman the council for national policy is the fucking mob boss let me tell you about them
the new york times describes the cnp as a little-known club of a few hundred of the most
powerful conservatives in the country who meet three times a year behind closed doors at undisclosed
locations for a confidential conference they are so secretive that you can only attend with
unanimous approval of executive committee and members are instructed to not even refer to the
organization by name like it's fucking fight club and because reality is stranger than fiction they
were founded in 1981 by the author of the left behind series tim la hay to tell you more about
them we need to go back in the past we have to go all the way back to 1845 when the southern baptist
convention was started the southern baptists were created because they branched away from baptists
uh over slavery southern baptists supported slavery the southern baptist convention remained
apart from other protestant denominations during the war and in 1962 the supreme court ended
public school prayer now they are mad it's at this time that the southern baptist realized that with
the shifting demographic of america that they might be irrelevant very soon they could not have it that
way so the southern baptist church plotted to get into politics and in 1979 southern baptist preacher
jerry falwell who was for segregation he was vehemently opposed to racial integration and academy
he decided to convene a meeting with some other pastors as well as republican operative
paul wyrick who co-founded the heritage foundation and falwell wyrick pat robinson tim la hay the author
of the freaking left behind series and presidential ronald reagan got together they started a little
501c3 organization called the council for national policy which is now a network of evangelicals oil
barons gun lobbyists and republican operatives working to dismantle the social safety net and
civil liberties that we have today and some of its more prominent members today include the coke
brothers and the devoss family leaders of this group have included tony perkins the head of the
lgbt bashing family research council who was vice president for a year and is still on its board of
governors tony perkins who once claimed that gay people recruit children and secretly published a
mailing list for a candidate he was managing from former clan leader david duke also on the cnp's board
of governors is michael perotka perotka was for many years on the board of the league of the south
and neo-confederate hate group that advocates for a newly secluded south ruled by white people
another board member is matt staver leader of the anti-lgbt liberty council who has worked for the
recriminalization of homosexuality and calls the boy scouts a playground for child abusers he likened
lgbt activists to terrorists and there's alan sears the founder of oh look alliance defending freedom
the ad fucking f the entire group seeks a fusion of fundamentalist theology with american civic life
they believe that this country was founded for christians like them generally natural born citizens
and white this group owns media outlets you might recognize this cnp member charlie kirk who runs
something called turning point usa the daily caller is also owned by members of the council for national
policy and so is breitbart guess what other organization is a part of the cnp the fucking national
rifle association the nra the seven mountains mandates adf moms of liberty alec they are all
arms of this fucking monster the cnp they backed ted cruz on his presidential run because his dad
rafael cruz was one of the founding fucking members amy coney barrett donald trump ronda santis
ted cruz they've all been speakers at cnp conferences you know those secret conferences that
they're not even allowed to say the dang name of or even disclose where they're having it yeah all
this time the republicans talking about how there's a shadowy government it was them all the fucking
time the cnp the council for national policy remember that name notice it when it pops up in articles or
on news stations because that is the organization that is behind all of the shit that is trying to
turn america into a white supremacist christian nationalist fascist shithole the cnp